I don't have to view Obama as the sole proprietor of prosperity.
I can look to people and say, oh, we had people before now that showed there was corruption in these spaces.
That's not enough.
It's not enough for you to just have more melanin than the average Caucasian.
It's not enough.
It's not valuable to be put in positions of power over terror.
If you're not ending the terror.
Hello, Brandon.
What's going on?
So what's that?
What's that?
I know you got thoughts on things.
Of course.
Always.
To me, at that point, that's where Africa serves as such a good reminder oftentimes that black people.
Get me there, Brandon.
Get me there.
Yeah.
A lot of people don't look at things from a pan-African view.
If you look at it in strictly a U.S. context, then this is the first time we've seen a nigga get in this position and wild out.
You know what I'm saying?
And do something crazy.
But when you recognize that you are a descendant of chattel slavery, oftentimes from Western Central Africa, and you look to these countries and see that we're from the most diverse continent on the globe.
So it makes all the sense in the world that we have such variation in our taste, in our expression, so on and so forth.
And it's why, for me, I don't feel the push or I no longer feel like, why can't we all see things the same way?
Like, we all black.
Like, white people said that.
I haven't liked this nigga people for 800 years.
Before I spoke this language, I didn't like what they was on.
You know what I'm saying?
And I think now when I'm bringing that back to, like, viewing it from an African perspective and seeing the amount of corruption that they have in these completely black places.
And you don't even have to go to Africa.
You look to Atlanta.
But whatever the case may be, a black faces in high spaces won't save us.
It has not, it's not a new phenomenon.
That's been the case for centuries.